# Farzin Maksud Mansuri

Ahmedabad, Gujarat maksudmansuri2100@gmail.com +91 9664934363

To be an integral part of an organization, holding a responsible and challenging position wherein I can apply my technical and interpersonal skills efficiently while gaining valuable experience and exposure each day.

## Work Experience

## Student Success Manager (Canada)

Azent Overseas Education-Ahmedabad, Gujarat May 2022 to Present

#### **Back Office Admission Executive (B2B)**

Global Colliance - Ahmedabad, Gujarat August 2020 to April 2022

#### **Admission Counselor**

The Smart Test Prep - Ahmedabad, Gujarat January 2020 to July 2020

## Sr. Admin Executive

Noesis Education and Visa Consultancy August 2017 to December 2019

#### **Administration and Front Desk**

Xpertise Education Consultancy June 2017 to August 2017

## Education

## Bachelors in ARTS - Economic

L.D ARTS COLLEGE - Ahmedabad, Gujarat 2013 to 2016

## Skills / IT Skills

 Ability to work in a fast-paced environment, highly organized with a creative flair, Enthusiasticselfstarter who contributes to the team.

#### Additional Information

- Ability to work in a fast-paced environment to set deadlines.
- Highly organized with a creative flair for project work
- Enthusiastic self-starter who contributes well to the team

#### **MANAGEMENT**

- Capable of adjusting to any kind of environment.
- Positive attitude.
- Dedicated towards goal.
- Confident in my ability to manage.
- Working in a team and individually.
- Like to face any challenges.
- Possess excellent decision-making and time-management skills.
- Ability to work under pressure and handle multiple tasks.

## **COMMUNICATION**

- Excellent oral and written correspondence with exceptional attention to detail
- Good representing skills

Fluent English speaking

#### Achievement

• Google Reviews